

Anton Zarubin

Senior Node.js Developer / Team Leader

Contact

+380 98 9309333

anton.zarubin@gmail.com

anton_zarubin

github.com/zarant77

npmjs.com/~zarant77

Summary

About ten years experience in PHP development.

Extensive experience in programming engineering and algorithm development.

Over three years experience in Node.js development.

Strong skills in development and implementation.

Abilities in inventing solutions, algorithms, methods and approaches.

Well skilled in database design and system architecture design.

Strong skill in "Single Page Application" development.

Good attention to details.

Native languages - Russian and Ukrainian. Conversational English.

Education

Graduated from Kharkiv National University of Radio Electronics in 2007, Masters Degree. Kharkiv, Ukraine.

M.S. in Computer Science, major in Computer Data Processing Systems.

Skills

OS/Platform

1	Windows 18 years (since 1998)	****
	Linux 12 years (since 2004)	****
	FreeBSD 2 years	***

Programming Language

JS	JavaScript 12 years (since 2004)	****
百	HTML 12 years (since 2004)	****
巨	CSS 12 years (since 2004)	****
Php	PHP 10 years	****
©	C++ 2 years	★★★☆☆
	Java 1 year	★★☆☆☆

NoSQL DBMS

•	MongoDB 1 year	****
	Couchbase 2 years	****
	Elasticsearch 2 years	****
	Redis 4 years (since 2012)	****

Relational DBMS

	MS SQL 3 years	****
En Se	MySQL 12 years (since 2004)	****
	PostgreSQL 1 year	★★★☆☆

ORM

	Sequelize 3 years (since 2013)	****
MONGÖÖSE:	Mongoose 1 year	****

Team Collaboration Tools

*	Git 5 years	****
	Subversion 5 years	****
X,	JIRA 2 years	****
	Redmine 1 year	****
心	Target Process 1 year	★★★☆☆

Network Technologies

REST	HTTP(S) REST 5 years (since 2011)	****
O A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A A	OAuth (1, 2) 1 year	***
30	WebSockets 1 year	***

Tools/Frameworks

	Node.js 4 years (since 2012)	****
express	Express.js 4 years (since 2012)	****
hapi	HAPI Less than a year	****
<u>U</u>	jQuery 7 years (since 2009)	****
A	Angular 1 year	★★★☆☆
×	Backbone Less than a year	
	React Less than a year	****
	NW.js Less than a year	****
	PhoneGap Less than a year	
	Cordova Less than a year	
JADE	Jade 4 years (since 2012)	****
{less}	LESS 4 years (since 2012)	****
Sass	SASS Less than a year	****
В	Bootstrap 4 years (since 2012)	****
Mi	Material-UI 12 years (since 2004)	***

Other Tools

Gulp	Gulp 1 year	****
	Grunt 4 years (since 2012)	****
шш	NPM 4 years (since 2012)	****
3	Bower 4 years (since 2012)	****
API DOC	ApiDoc 2 years (since 2014)	****
<i>57</i> MΓ	RAML 1 year	★★★☆☆
(€-)	Swagger 1 year	★★★☆☆
mocha	Mocha 4 years (since 2012)	****
JS Hint	JSHint 2 years (since 2014)	****

Experience

2014 - Present time, Node.js Developer

Freelancer (Odesk/Upwork) http://upwork.com/



More than year I used to work remotely for MarketWave. (http://www.market-wave.com/) MarketWave is company who provide customer multi-channels management (Phone, Live Chat, etc). Company provide sales support for visitors with key leaders of e-commerce. They was my general clients.

Primary Responsibilities:

Design, develop, test and deploy web applications

Develop appropriate code structures to solve specific tasks according to standards

Fix bugs, troubleshoot and resolve problems

Build flexible data models and seamless integration points

Comment code and write documentation using ApiDoc

Code review

Used technologies and tools:

Platforms: Node.js

Frameworks: Express, Angular, Bootstrap

Databases: MS SQL, Couchbase, Elasticsearch

Documentation: ApiDoc

QA: Mocha, JSHint

Another tools: Less, Jade, Grunt, Bower, NPM

2012 - 2014, Team Leader / Project Manager

QCoders http://qcoders.com/



During work in this company I had only one general project which was divided to few small subprojects. InTouch http://intouch.inweb24.us/ InTouch is a email marketing system. Like MailChimp or Mandrill but with an emphasis in network marketing. I'm started this project from scratch. Gradually our team has grown up to 7 developers. It was first experience with Node.js on commercial project.

Primary Responsibilities:

Project management

Team management (team of seven members)

Estimating and resource planning

Design and development of system architecture

Design and development of source code

Database design and development

GUI design

Code review

Used technologies and tools:

Platforms: Node.js

Frameworks: Express, Backbone, Bootstrap

Databases: MongoDB Documentation: RAML

QA: Mocha

Another tools: Less, Jade, Grunt, Bower, NPM

2011 - 2012, Senior Software Developer / Team Leader

Quadecco http://quadecco.de/



Development of many projects for outsourcing company using following technologies

Primary Responsibilities:

Team management

Estimating and resource planning

Design and development of system architecture

Design and development of source code

Database design and development

GUI design

Code review

Used technologies and tools:

Platforms: PHP, Javascript, HTML, CSS

Frameworks: YII, Zend Framework, jQuery, Mootools

Databases: MySQL, MSSQL

2009 - 2011, Senior Software Developer / Team Leader

ZFort Group http://www.zfort.com.ua/



Development of many projects for outsourcing company using following technologies

Primary Responsibilities:

Team management

Estimating and resource planning

Design and development of system architecture

Design and development of source code

Database design and development

GUI design

Code review

Used technologies and tools:

Platforms: PHP, Javascript, HTML, CSS

Frameworks: YII, PRADO, Zend Framework, jQuery

Databases: MySQL

2007 - 2009, Software Developer

Intetics Co http://intetics.com/



Development of many projects for outsourcing company using following technologies

Primary Responsibilities:

Code development

Database development

Used technologies and tools:

Platforms: PHP, Javascript, HTML, CSS

Frameworks: jQuery Databases: MySQL

2005 - 2006, Junior Software Developer

Letwork http://www.letwork.com/



Development of many projects for outsourcing company using following technologies

Primary Responsibilities:

Code development

Database development

Used technologies and tools:

Platforms: PHP, Javascript, HTML, CSS

Databases: MySQL